(Amy:)On the bright side,
every six-year-old there
(Amy:)was jealous of my tiara.
(Amy:)Not gonna lie, it felt good.
(Penny:)When did you guys
start feeling grown up?
'Cause I am not sure I do.
(Bernadette:)Honestly, I thought when
I got married I would,
(Bernadette:)but I still kind of feel
like I'm pretending.
(Bernadette:)It doesn't help that most of
my clothes come from Gap Kids.
(Penny:)Okay, so I'm an adult,
(Penny:)and the other day I saw
an old man slip and fall down,
(Penny:)and I laughed.
(Penny:)I mean, I laughed hard.
(Penny:)Like, out loud.
(Penny:)If he was conscious,
he would've heard me.
-Oh, my gosh.
-I know.
(Penny:)One of the tennis balls
came off his walker
(Penny:)and bounced right off his head.
I mean....
(Penny:)I almost wet myself.
(Penny:)I guess you had to be there.
(Amy:)I think I have you both beat.
(Amy:)Imagine trying to feel
like a grown-up
(Amy:)when you've never
even been with a man.
(Penny:)Sex is not what makes you a grown-up.